powerchallenge.com 2007-12-22

# Privacy Policy

Power Challenge Sweden AB

PRIVACY POLICY 

(Revised 6th November 2006)

YOUR USE OF OUR SERVICES AND WEB SITES IS SUBJECT TO YOUR AGREEMENT TO THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY.  
Power Challenge Sweden AB. ("PCS") respects your privacy and is committed to protecting the personal information that you may provide while using our web sites and services. This Privacy Policy (the "Policy") is intended to provide you with notice of the following:

The web sites and services covered by this Policy 

All content on the powerchallenge.com domain, Powerfootball.se domain and related domains (The game Power Soccer and Football  League).

Our policies concerning children 

PCS complies with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act and all other applicable laws and regulations concerning children and the Internet.

Children under the age of 13

Because our Sites are not directed to children under the age of 13, PCS does not provide memberships to persons under age 13. If you are under the age of 13, you may not create an account on the Site, you may not sign up for any subscription service or buy anything through the Store, and you are not eligible to enter any of our competitions. Except as may be required by law, PCS will not knowingly collect, maintain, or disclose any personal information from children under the age of 13.

Kids between the ages of 13 and 18

If you are between the ages of 13 and 18, please let your parent or guardian know about this Policy and get his or her permission before you give us any of your personal identifiable information. Don't post your real name on a web site or message board, and never tell anyone online anything private about yourself or your family, including your phone number and address. Use screen names at all times. If you win a competition that has a prize, your parent or guardian will have to mail or fax us a signed note at the address or fax number listed in the rules for the specific contest that says it was OK for you to enter, and tells us they will accept the prize for you. 

Information for Parents/Guardians

PCS encourages parents and guardians to spend time online with their children to become familiar with the types of content available on the Internet, including our online games. Parents and guardians should regularly oversee their children's use of e-mail and other online communications and transactional features. Control tools are available from online services and software manufacturers that can help provide a safe online environment for kids.  
If you are a parent or guardian who has discovered that your child has submitted his or her personal information without your permission or consent, PCS will take reasonable steps to remove that information from the PCS database at your request. To request removal of your child's information, please send us an e-mail (to the address below) and be sure to include in your message the same user name, password, and email address that your child submitted. If your child has used your credit card on our web sites without your permission, contact us immediately at account@powerchallenge.com.

What personal information we collect from you 

General

We do not collect any personal information from you, unless you provide it to us voluntarily. If you decide to provide us your personal information (e.g., name, email address, and mailing address), we will only collect the personal information which is needed to fulfil your requests and our legitimate business objectives. 

Memberships and Registration

In order for you to register, we require you to provide us with an email address, sometimes birth date, gender, and real name. In order to pay for a certain feature on our sites additional information, such as your real name and billing information, will be required.  
You may be asked to choose a user name and password. Please do not use your real name or the real name of another person when selecting a user name. Please note that your user name will be available to the Internet's general public while you participate in some services, like chat rooms or message boards. Personal information disclosed by you within our chat areas, instant message service, message boards, or during game play can be collected by other users of such services and may result in unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for protecting such information that you may disclose to third parties through our services (e.g. sending your telephone number to another user through the chat service). To the extent that you create a public profile that may be available to others on our sites and services, you are solely responsible for its content and accuracy at all times. To edit, change, or delete such information, follow the instructions on the web site.

Email Newsletters and Friend to Friend Promotions

You must have a membership account in order to receive emails from us. You can op out of receiving future emailing from us by following the directions contained in the email to "unsubscribe." Also, except in jurisdictions where it may be prohibited by law to do so, some PCS sites and Services may ask you to submit information about other people. For example, we may offer "Tell a Friend" promotions. In these situations, users are asked to provide the e-mail address and, sometimes, the name of a friend. After the "Tell a Friend" transaction is completed, that information is deleted. 

Contests and Promotions

To participate in some of our competitions, contests, tournaments, cups, and other promotions, you may be asked to provide additional personal information such as your mailing address. In each such case, no new personal information will be collected from you without your consent. This information may be collected by PCS or by third parties such as co-sponsors or vendors for the promotion. PCS's use of any such information will be governed by this Policy. The names of third parties such as co-sponsors (other than vendors hired by PCS to conduct, administer, and execute a promotion on behalf of PCS) will be disclosed to you when you are asked to sign up for the promotion. You should review such third parties' privacy policies to see how they may use any information that they collect.

Online Purchases and Technical Support

When you buy credits to activate extra features in the games, we will also require that you provide us with the necessary billing information such as your real name, credit card information, street address, etc., so that we may provide the service.  
Issues related to customer service, billing questions, technical and computer support, etc. may also require you to provide us with some personal information so that we may resolve the issue properly.

Online Games

When you play any of the games offered and/or served by PCS, or use any of the communication features on the Sites, your IP address (the Internet protocol address from which you access any of the above) may be stored in our records. Our update service routine may check your computer to see that you have the most recent version of game-specific files; when you communicate within any game or any other communication feature (e.g. live chat, instant message services), even "privately" to another person, you do so with the understanding that those communications go through our servers, can be logged and monitored by us, you have no expectation of privacy in any of those communications and, accordingly, you expressly consent to monitoring of communications (including technical support and customer service communications) that you send and receive. When you log into our online games, your system specifications (such as OS, web browser, java version, RAM, video card, monitor, system configuration, etc.) may be reviewed/recorded by us for the purposes of analyzing and optimizing your game experience and in order to provide you with customer service. Sometimes we may review/record an automatic log file created from the game. The log file contains information about your latest match played and some information about your system specifications such as processor, video card, system configuration, etc. We use these files to track down and find bugs in the game to be able to make the game better. 

What non-personal information we collect from you 

General, aggregated, demographic, and non-personal information may be collected by PCS. It will not be linked to any of your personal information, through cookies or other means, without your consent. This type of anonymous, aggregated profiling and session data may include information that you have provided to us through surveys, polls, etc., but will not be tied to any personal information, without your consent. It may also include aggregated anonymous information about site usage and the customer base.  
In many cases, PCS will automatically collect certain non-personal information about your use of its sites and services. PCS might collect, among other things, information concerning the type of Internet browser or computer operating system you are using, the domain name of your Internet service provider, your "click path" through the PCS site, and the web site or advertisement that was linked to or from the PCS site when you visited. To do this, PCS may use cookies and other technology (see below). Your visits to our web sites, and information provided through these technologies, will be anonymous unless you provide us with personal information or have provided such information in the past. For example, if you've created a membership account, your account information (including name, email address, and billing and shipping information) may be linked to the items you purchased (i.e., billing history).

This game incorporates advertisement serving technology, which allows certain items, objects or images (e.g. advertisements) to be placed in the game via your PC, MAC or console.  The technology collects information about the PC, MAC or console and the IP address on which the game is played and information on how the game is played, in particular regarding interactions with the advertisements served into the game and other items.  This information is processed by a third party provider of advertisement serving technology for purposes of calculating fees owed by advertisers and monitoring advertisement efficiency. Your IP address and other information described above may be sent to a foreign jurisdiction for processing via the Internet. That third party provider will not know who you are or try to identify or contact you. By playing the game and accepting our rules and privacy policy you consent to data processing. In some jurisdictions, IP addresses may be viewed legally as personally identifiable information. You hereby acknowledge and agree to PCS collection and use of your IP address as non-Personal Information even though your ip address may be viewed legally as personally identifiable information. By the use of this game, you hereby consent to the temporary upload of the Placements to your PC; and the Non-Personal Information being collected and shared with third parties.

Information on cookies and related technology

PCS web sites, and some services and advertisements on such sites, may contain "cookies." A cookie is a piece of data that is sent to your browser, which will store the cookie on your computer if your browser is enabled to accept cookies. Clear gifs (also known as "web beacons") assist in the delivery of cookies.  
PCS uses cookies, clear gifs, frames, server log analysis and other technology to customize your experience with our sites and services. Personal information collected through the use of these technologies will be handled according to this Policy.  
Most internet browsers will allow you to erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block acceptance of cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. You should refer to your browser instructions or "Help" screen to learn more about how to manage cookies. Please note, however, that if you block cookies, some portions of the PCS web sites and services may not function properly.  
PCS does not control cookies in third party ads, and visitors are encouraged to check the privacy policies of advertisers and/or ad services to learn about their use of cookies and other technology. The ads appearing on our Web sites may be delivered to you by third-party advertising companies. These companies may use information about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

How we use and share the information that we collect from you

Personal information which we collect for a particular purpose will only be saved and used for that purpose, unless you have agreed to allow us to use it for some other purpose, as described in this Policy. For example, if you make an online purchase, and unless you have given us permission to do otherwise, we will only collect and save the personal information you provided to us, including your billing and delivery information, in order to (1) complete the sale, (2) comply with tax and other applicable statutes, (3) maintain accurate business and financial records (in accordance with accepted standards), and (4) assist with customer service and returns.  
When you have provided personal information to us for a particular purpose, we may disclose your information to other companies that we have engaged to assist us in fulfilling your request. This may include, but is not limited to, fulfilment houses, billing services, transaction managers, credit verification services, and other third party service providers. We may also disclose any of your personal information to law enforcement or other appropriate third parties in connection with criminal investigations, investigation of fraud, infringement of intellectual property rights, or other suspected illegal activities, or as otherwise may be required by applicable law, or, as we deem necessary in our sole discretion, in order to protect the legitimate legal and business interests of PCS.   
We may use the information we collect from you for the purpose of providing you with technical support, customer service, and account maintenance. We use the information we collect to learn what you like, tailor your experience accordingly, and to improve web sites and our other products. We send e-mail to our members who want to receive e-mail from us. However, if you don't want to receive e-mail from us, you can unsubscribe on the e-mail received

Except as described in this policy, we will not give any of your personal information to any third party without your express approval, and the only personal information we will ask you if you want us to share with third parties is your name, your mailing address and e-mail address. We sometimes share general, demographic, or aggregated (not personal) information with third parties about our user base, but that information does not include any personal information.  
You will be deemed to have consented to the disclosure to, and use by, a subsequent owner or operator of the Sites, of any personal information contained in the PCS database for such site, if PCS or one of its companies assigns all of its rights and obligations regarding the use of your personal information at the time of a bankruptcy, merger, acquisition, sale of all or substantially all of PCS's or such PCS company's assets to a subsequent owner or operator, or similar event.

Information about links and third parties related to our sites and services

This Policy applies only to information collected online by PCS through web sites maintained by PCS and affiliated companies that PCS may own or control. From time to time, we may provide links to third party web sites. This Policy does not apply to third party web sites, whether we provide a link to such sites or not, so we encourage you to review the policies of all such sites carefully, as your rights will be governed by those third party policies and not by PCS's. Additionally, there may be unauthorized third party web sites that may be providing links from their sites to our web sites without our knowledge or control. We are not responsible for the content of any third party web sites, expressly disclaim any statements or assertions made on such web sites, and deny all liability associated with your use of, and the content on, such other sites or advertisements contained therein.

How you may access, change, or delete the information you have provided to us

If you change your mind and do not want to receive e-mails from us you may send an e-mail to us at account@powerchallenge.com. Subject to security and privacy concerns (e.g., regarding your password and credit card number), we will give you the ability to review, correct, delete, and/or update your information. To do so, you may send us an e-mail at account@powerchallenge.com. If you choose to have your personal information removed from our active databases, we will do so within a reasonable time after your request and we will take reasonable steps to ensure that your personal data is not used (except as may be required by law) by PCS after your notification to us.

Other important agreements that govern your use of our sites and services 

In addition to this Policy, your rights and obligations concerning our web sites, services, and online games are governed by the applicable web sites terms of use, and other applicable policies, rules, guidelines, and requirements. When you sign up to use our services, please review each such agreement carefully, as you must agree to be bound by each such agreement before you may use the service.

Language and location

By consenting to this Policy, you confirm that your command and knowledge of English (or in some cases, Portuguese, French, German, or Spanish) is sufficient to understand the terms and conditions set forth herein.  
For persons in European Union countries, as used herein, terms such as "personal information" refer to "personal data" as defined by the Directive 95/46/EC of the European Parliament and of the Council of 24 October 1995 on the protection of individuals with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data ("Directive"). We will not collect any personal data from you unless you provide it voluntarily by providing us with your freely given specific and informed consent. By using PCS websites or services, you agree that we may transfer your personal information outside the European Union in connection with the purposes stated in this Policy. Your personal data may be transferred outside EU (and/or other non-EU jurisdictions, as applicable).   
In certain countries, some of our online games and the services related thereto, may be provided to you by third party distribution partners. To the extent that a third party distributor is providing services related to your account, you understand and agree that each such distributor will collect and use your personal information in accordance with its own privacy policies (which you will have access to when you register to play). To the extent that PCS collects or retains any of your personal information, its use will continue to be governed by the terms of this Policy. 

Our commitment to secure the personal information we have collected

While PCS takes precautions against possible breaches in its web sites and customer databases, no web site or Internet transmission is completely secure. Consequently, PCS cannot guarantee that unauthorized access, hacking, data loss, or other breaches will never occur. Your use of the PCS sites and services is at your own risk. PCS urges you to take steps to keep your personal information safe by memorizing your password or keeping it in a safe place (separate from your account information), logging out of your user account, and closing your web browser.  
Whenever you give PCS sensitive or confidential information (for example, credit card numbers for purchases), PCS will take commercially reasonable steps to protect the information by establishing a secure connection with your web browser. PCS employs a security technology to protect the transmission of payment information to the site. Unless otherwise specified herein or on the site where you make a purchase, credit card numbers are used only for payment processing and are not retained for marketing purposes.

Notice of changes to the Policy

PCS reserves the right to change this Policy at any time by notifying registered users via e-mail of the existence of a new Policy and/or posting the new Policy on the PCS sites. All changes to the Policy will be effective when posted, and your continued use of any PCS site or service after the posting will constitute your acceptance of, and agreement to be bound by, those changes.
